A Register of the Ivan Alekseevich Poliakov Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, 1942-1969 and undated.
  - Latyshev, Sergei Nikolaevich, 1960-1966 and undated (Folder 13: 7)
  - Lavrov, Aleksandr Nikolaevich, 1953-1956 (Folder 13: 8)
  - Lebedev, Arkadii Timofeevich, 1950 (Folder 13: 9)
  - Lebedev, Oleg Ivanovich, 1953-1959 (Folder 13: 10)
  - Lebedinskaia, Militsa Stefanovna, 1960 and undated (Folder 13: 11)
  - Leonidov, Aleksei Aleksandrovich, 1959-1960 (Folder 13: 12)
  - Leonov, Petr Grigor'evich, 1955 (Folder 13: 13)
  - Leontii (Turkevich), Metropolitan, 1954 (Folder 13: 14)
  - Lewis, Barbara, 1966 (Folder 13: 15)
  - Life, 1952-1958 (Folder 13: 16)
  - Liubel'skii, Nikolai Aleksandrovich, 1954 (Folder 13: 17)
  - Liubimov, Ignatii, Reverend, 1953-1954 (Folder 13: 18)
  - Liubimov, N., 1955 (Folder 13: 19)
  - Liubomudrov, V. V., 1963 and undated (Folder 13: 20)
  - Lodge, Anna Osipovna, Nucia, 1966-1967 (Folder 13: 21)
  - London, Ivan D., 1965-1966 (Folder 13: 22)
  - Lozin, Petr Vladimirovich, 1968 (Folder 13: 23)
  - Lukashkin, Anatolii Safronovich, 1963 (Folder 13: 24)
  - Lukich, Sergei, 1952 (Folder 13: 25)
  - Lygin, Mikhail Maksimovich, 1953-1968 and undated (Folder 13: 26)
  - Magerovskii, Lev F., 1953 (Folder 13: 27)
  - Makarenkov, Aleksandr, Reverend, 1953-1956 (Folder 13: 28)
  - Makarov, Georgii Emel'ianovich, 1948-1953 and undated. (Folder 13: 29)
    Includes "Mysli starogo kazaka"
  - Makhin, Ivan K., 1950-1955 and undated (Folder 13: 30)
  - Maksimov, David Pavlovich, 1955-1960 (Folder 13: 31)
  - Maksimov, Vitalii Ivanovich, 1957 (Folder 13: 32)
  - Malikov, Aleksandr, 1953 (Folder 13: 33)
  - Malkov, Petr, 1962 (Folder 13: 34)
  - Mal'kovskaia, Kira Mikhailovna, 1956 (Folder 13: 35)
  - Mamontov, Nikolai Ivanovich, 1956-1957 and undated (Folder 13: 36)
  - Mamontova, Ekaterina Vasil'evna, 1952-1958 and undated (Folder 13: 37)
  - Manakin, Viktor Konstantinovich, 1953 (Folder 13: 38)
  - Manchenkov, Ivan Pavlovich, 1962 (Folder 13: 39)
  - Markotuk, Margarita Oksanovna, 1953 (Folder 14: 1)
  - Markovich, Vladimir Zakhar'evich, 1964 (Folder 14: 2)
  - Mashevskii, K. P., 1962-1963 (Folder 14: 3)
  - Mashintsev, Ivan Vasil'evich, 1932-1957 (Folder 14: 4)
  - Maybohm (Meibom), Fedor Fedorovich, 1953 and undated (Folder 14: 5)
  - McCarthy, Joseph, 1957 and undated (Folder 14: 6)
  - Medvedev, Petr Ivanovich, 1950-1958 (Folder 14: 7)
  - Megliuevich, Makarii Pavlovich, 1952-1959 (Folder 14: 8)
  - Megliuevich, Vera Vasil'evna, 1953 (Folder 14: 9)
  - Meleshkevich, Vasilii Stepanovich, 1957 (Folder 14: 10)
  - Meleshkevich, Viktor Konstantinovich, 1953 (Folder 14: 11)
  - Meleshkov, Mr., 1960 (Folder 14: 12)
  - Mel'zhev, Nikolai Aleksandrovich, 1956-1962 (Folder 14: 13)
  - Miach, Vasilii Pavlovich, 1962-1964 (Folder 14: 14)
  - Migulin, S., 1967 (Folder 14: 15)
  - Mikhailichenko, S., 1956-1957 (Folder 14: 16)
  - Mikhailik, M. S., 1952-1958 (Folder 14: 17)
  - Mikhailov, Anatolii Petrovich, 1957-1962 and undated (Folder 14: 18)
  - Mikhailov, Georgii, 1953 (Folder 14: 19)
  - Mikhailov, Timofei Vasil'evich, 1949-1962 (Folder 14: 20)
  - Mikhailov, Viktor Vasil'evich, 1952-1962 (Folder 14: 21)
  - Mikheev, Leonid Mikhailovich and Agniia Mikhailovna, 1952-1961 (Folder 14: 22)
  - Miklashevskaia, Nonna, 1959 (Folder 14: 23)
  - Milov, Boris Nikolaevich, 1956-1969 (Folder 14: 24)
  - Minaev, Mikhail, Reverend, 1953-1955 (Folder 14: 25)
  - Mitkevich, Grigorii Grigorievich, 1957-1962 (Folder 14: 26)
  - Moiseev, Mitrofan Alekseevich, 1953-1965 and undated (Folder 14: 27)
  - Mogilevskii, P. V., 1949 (Folder 15: 1)
  - Mokryi, Il'ia Nikolaevich, 1949 (Folder 15: 2)
  - Molchanov, Vasilii Nikiforovich, 1952-1965 (Folder 15: 3)
  - Morgunov, Stepan Nikolaevich, 1960-1962 (Folder 15: 4)
  - Morozov, Vasilii Ivanovich, 1947-1949 (Folder 15: 5)
  - Morozovich, P. A., 1953 (Folder 15: 6)
  - Myl'nikov, Vladimir Stepanovich, 1955-1956 (Folder 15: 7)
  - Nagibin, Evgenii Sergeevich and Liudmila Mikhailovna, 1956-1963 (Folder 15: 8)
  - Naumenko, Viacheslav Grigorievich, 1945-1958 and undated (Folder 15: 9)
  - Nazarenko, Nikolai Grigorievich, 1958 (Folder 15: 10)
  - Nechkin, Nikolai Panfilovich, 1955-1961 (Folder 15: 11)
  - Nedozhogin, Ivan Patrikievich, 1955 and undated (Folder 15: 12)
  - Nefedov, Aleksandr Alekseevich, 1952-1955 (Folder 15: 13)
  - Nefedov, Pavel Ivanovich, 1952-1953 (Folder 15: 14)
  - Neizvestnyi, N., 1953 (Folder 15: 15)
  - Nemov, Mikhail Ivanovich
    - 1955-1959 (Folder 15: 16)
    - 1960-1965 (Folder 15: 17)
  - Nikolaev, Ivan, 1954 (Folder 15: 18)
  - Nikolaev, Konstantin Nikolaevich, 1953-1963 (Folder 15: 19)
  - Nikolaevskii, Lev L'vovich, 1955-1963 (Folder 15: 20)
  - Nikolich, Georgii Kuz'mich, 1959 (Folder 15: 21)
  - Nikol'skaia, Kseniia Dmitrievna, 1963-1965 (Folder 15: 22)
  - Nikon (Rklitskii), Archbishop, 1960-1962 (Folder 15: 23)
  - Nevkovich, V., 1958 (Folder 16: 1)
  - Novoe russkoe slovo, 1954-1968 and undated (Folder 16: 2)
  - Olifirenko, T. D., 1960-1962 (Folder 16: 3)
  - Obolenskii, Sergei, 1953 (Folder 16: 4)
  - Onoprienko, Aleksandr Aleksandrovich, 1953 (Folder 16: 5)
  - Oprits, Il'ia Nikolaevich, 1955-1961 (Folder 16: 6)
  - Ordovskii-Tanaevskii, Nikolai Nikolaevich, 1957 (Folder 16: 7)
  - Orekhov, Vasilii Vasil'evich, 1948-1965 (Folder 16: 8)
  - Orlov, Tikhon Ivanovich, 1956 (Folder 16: 9)
  - Padalkin, A., 1959 (Folder 16: 10)
  - Patkovskii, B., 1953-1954 (Folder 16: 11)
  - Pavliusik, Georgii, Reverend, 1955 (Folder 16: 12)
  - Pavlov, S. P., undated (Folder 16: 13)
  - Pekhovskii, Karnei Karneevich, 1965 (Folder 16: 14)
  - Perepelkin, A. P., 1969 (Folder 16: 15)
  - Persianov, Dmitrii Andreevich, 1949-1962 and undated (Folder 16: 16)
  - Petropulo, G. N., 1962 (Folder 16: 17)
  - Petrov, Pavel Vasil'evich, 1953-1954 (Folder 16: 18)
  - Pikulin, Il'ia Efimovich, 1959 (Folder 16: 19)
  - Pisarevskii, Ivan Konstantinovich, 1960-1962 (Folder 16: 20)
  - Plokhii, Kondrat Alekseevich, 1964 (Folder 16: 21)
  - Pochovskii, Andrei Vasil'evich, 1952 (Folder 16: 22)
  - Pokhlebkin, Sviatoslav Mikhailovich and Nina Viacheslavna, 1950-1959 (Folder 16: 23)
  - Poliakov, A., 1954-1955 (Folder 16: 24)
  - Poliakov, Semen K. and Zoia Aleksandrovna, 1955-1960 (Folder 16: 25)
  - Poliakov, Sergei Petrovich, 1953-1958 (Folder 16: 26)
  - Poliakov, Vladimir Aleksandrovich, 1952-1965 (Folder 16: 27)
  - Poliakova, K., 1965 (Folder 17: 1)
  - Polish American Congress, 1956 (Folder 17: 2)
  - Polkovnikov, Iurii Georgievich, 1953-1955 (Folder 17: 3)
  - Polkovnikov, Sergei Petrovich, 1957-1965 (Folder 17: 4)
  - Poluboiarov, Nikolai Fedorovich, 1955-1965 (Folder 17: 5)
  - Polukhin, Georgii Dmitrievich, 1953 (Folder 17: 6)
  - Polukina, Elena Afanas'evna, 1952-1953 and undated (Folder 17: 7)
  - Pomeranenko, Vladimir Vasil'evich, 1954-1956 (Folder 17: 8)
  - Ponomarenko, Vl., 1955 (Folder 17: 9)
  - Popov, Mikhail Fedorovich, 1956 and undated (Folder 17: 10)
  - Popov, Mikhail Iakovlevich, 1960-1961 (Folder 17: 11)
  - Popov, Nikolai Dmitrievich, 1953-1959 (Folder 17: 12)
  - Popov, Nikolai Ivanovich, 1956 (Folder 17: 13)
  - Popov, Sergei L'vovich, 1956 (Folder 17: 14)
  - Popov, Timofei Timofeevich, 1948-1953 (Folder 17: 15)
  - Popov, Viktor Ivanovich, 1955-1960 (Folder 17: 16)
  - Popova, Pelagiia A., 1953 (Folder 17: 17)
  - Postupal'skii, Nikolai Sergeevich, 1956 (Folder 17: 18)
  - Pozdnyshev, Sergei Dmitrievich
    - 1945-1957 (Folder 17: 19)
    - 1958-1968 (Folder 17: 20)
  - Pozhidaev, Vsevolod Vasil'evich, 1955 (Folder 17: 21)
  - Prazhmo, Nina Fedorovna, 1956-1961 and undated (Folder 17: 22)
  - Prokhorov, Pimen, undated (Folder 17: 23)
  - Pronin, A., 1962 (Folder 17: 24)
  - Pshenikhin, Grigorii, 1954 (Folder 17: 25)
  - Puchkov, F., 1952 (Folder 17: 26)
  - Pukhliakov, Sergei Vasil'evich, 1955-1961 (Folder 17: 27)
  - Puettner, Ludmila Pavlovna, 1951 (Folder 17: 28)
  - Radchenkov, Mikhail Samoilovich, 1956 (Folder 17: 29)
  - Radostovets, Vasilii Aleksandrovich, 1961 (Folder 17: 30)
  - Rasteriaev, Konstantin Rodionovich, 1959 (Folder 17: 31)
  - Ravnitskii, S. G., 1965 (Folder 17: 32)
  - Ray, M., undated (Folder 17: 33)
  - Rebrov, Sergei Aleksandrovich, 1957 and undated (Folder 18: 1)
  - Regis, Felipe, Reverend, 1953 (Folder 18: 2)
  - Remiskevich, S., 1955-1956 (Folder 18: 3)
  - Retivova, Novela Evgen'evna, 1960 (Folder 18: 4)
  - Reutskii, Dmitrii Maksimovich, 1952-1956 (Folder 18: 5)
  - Riabinin, Aleksandr Isidorovich, 1963 (Folder 18: 6)
  - Riabukhin, Boris Vladimirovich, 1952 (Folder 18: 7)
  - Riabukhin, Nikandr Mikhailovich, 1955 (Folder 18: 8)
  - Riasnianskii, Sergei Nikolaevich, 1955-1965 and undated (Folder 18: 9)
  - Rodimyi krai, undated (Folder 18: 10)
  - Rodionov, V., 1957 (Folder 18: 11)
  - Raev, A., 1953 (Folder 18: 12)
  - Rogozhin, Anatolii Ivanovich, 1948-1963 (Folder 18: 13)
  - Romanov, Pavel Andreevich, 1958 (Folder 18: 14)
  - Romanova, Vera Konstantinovna, 1953 (Folder 18: 15)
  - Rossiiskaia nezavisimost', 1963 (Folder 18: 16)
  - Rossiiskie natsional'nye ob"edineniia, 1956 and undated (Folder 18: 17)
  - Rostovtseva, Elizaveta, 1959 and undated (Folder 18: 18)
  - Rotov, Aleksandr Aleksandrovich, 1953-1959 (Folder 18: 19)
  - Rotov, Mikhail Mikhailovich, 1957-1965 (Folder 18: 20)
  - Rubanov, Lev Stepanovich, 1953 (Folder 18: 21)
  - Rubashkin, Georgii Georgievich, 1952-1962 (Folder 18: 22)
  - Rubtsov, Artem, 1953-1956 (Folder 18: 23)
  - Rudov, Semen Petrovich, 1953-1956 (Folder 18: 24)
  - Rummel, Aleksandr Vasil'evich, 1961-1965. (Folder 18: 25)
    Includes circulars and internal informational bulletins of Predstavitel'stvo rossiiskikh emigrantov v Amerike
  - Rusin, V., undated (Folder 18: 26)
  - Russkaia zhizn', 1959-1967 and undated (Folder 18: 27)
  - Rybakov, Nikolai Pavlovich, 1953-1965 (Folder 18: 28)
  - Rykovskaia, Ekaterina Ivanovna, 1958-1965 (Folder 18: 29)
  - Rykovskii, Vladimir Fedorovich, 1955-1959 (Folder 18: 30)
  - Ryzhkov, Mikhail Mikhailovich, 1954 (Folder 19: 1)
  - Sabel'nikov, Ivan, 1953 (Folder 19: 2)
  - Sadovskii, Boris Semenovich, 1967 (Folder 19: 3)
  - Sakhno-Ustimovich, Aleksei Alekseevich, 1955 (Folder 19: 4)
  - Sakhnovskii, Nikolai Ivanovich, 1956-1957 (Folder 19: 5)
  - Saks, Georgii Vladimirovich, 1961-1964 (Folder 19: 6)
  - Samsonov, Boris Dmitrievich, 1953-1956 (Folder 19: 7)
  - Samsonov, Evgenii Aleksandrovich, 1954-1967 and undated (Folder 19: 8)
  - Savva (Raevskii), Archbishop, 1955-1967 (Folder 19: 9)
  - Sargeant, Howland, 1954-1955. (Folder 19: 10)
    See also American Committee for Liberation
  - Sedliarov, E., 1963-1964 (Folder 19: 11)
  - Sedykh, A., 1964 (Folder 19: 12)
  - Sekretev, Aleksandr Lavrovich, 1954-1956 (Folder 19: 13)
  - Selianova, Ol'ga, 1958 (Folder 19: 14)
  - Semanitskii, Ioann, Reverend, undated (Folder 19: 15)
  - Semenov, Aleksei Ivanovich, 1943-1960 (Folder 19: 16)
  - Semenova, Kseniia Nikolaevna, 1951-1952 (Folder 19: 17)
  - Sengiul'er, N., 1960 and undated (Folder 19: 18)
  - Seniavin, Aleksandr Pavlovich, 1959-1961 (Folder 19: 19)
  - Serafim (Ivanov), Archbishop, 1963 (Folder 19: 20)
  - Serebrian, Sergei Nikolaevich, 1957-1964 (Folder 19: 21)
  - Sergievskii, Boris Vasil'evich, 1955-1968 and undated (Folder 19: 22)
  - Setsenevskii, A., 1957 (Folder 19: 23)
  - Shakhovskaia, Sofiia Il'inishna, 1956-1967 and undated (Folder 19: 24)
  - Shapkin, Vladimir Vasil'evich, 1960-1965 (Folder 19: 25)
  - Shchegolev, Pavel Innokent'evich, 1963 (Folder 19: 26)
  - Shchurov, Georgii Vladimirovich, 1959 (Folder 19: 27)
  - Shelek, Ol'ga, 1968 (Folder 19: 28)
  - Shenfelk, Miron Markovich, 1960 (Folder 19: 29)
  - Shepetkovskii, Ivan Aleksandrovich, 1949-1950 (Folder 19: 30)
  - Sherstobitov, Dmitrii Andreevich, 1955-1963 (Folder 19: 31)
  - Sherstobitova, Varvara Nikolaevna, 1959 and undated (Folder 19: 32)
  - Shevtsov, Tikhon, 1949 (Folder 19: 33)
  - Shevtsova, Mariia Zakharovna, 1956 and undated (Folder 19: 34)
  - Shimanskaia, Mrs., 1960 (Folder 19: 35)
  - Shliakhtin, Erast Erastovich, 1953-1963 (Folder 19: 36)
  - Shliakhtin, Vladimir Vasil'evich, 1955 (Folder 19: 37)
  - Shlykov, Mikhail Vasil'evich, 1959-1964 and undated (Folder 19: 38)
  - Shmeleva, Antonina Ivanovna, 1957 (Folder 19: 39)
  - Shul'gin, Georgii, 1956 (Folder 19: 40)
  - Shumilov, Anatolii Filippovich, 1967-1969 (Folder 19: 41)
  - Shupliak, Il'ia, 1953 (Folder 19: 42)
  - Sibilev, Georgii Alekseevich, 1952-1953 (Folder 19: 43)
  - Simbirtsev, Ivan, 1955 (Folder 19: 44)
  - Simmons, Lily, 1959-1964 and undated (Folder 19: 45)
  - Sirotin, Ivan Grigor'evich, 1955-1956 (Folder 19: 46)
  - Sitchenkov, Ivan Vladimirovich and Tatiana Antonovna (Box 20)
    - 1953-1960 (Folder 20: 1)
    - 1961-1968 (Folder 20: 2)
  - Skliarov, Ivan Konstantinovich, 1961-1968 (Folder 20: 3)
  - Skochko, I. P., 1955 and undated (Folder 20: 4)
  - Skvortsov, Mikhail Nikolaevich, 1953 (Folder 20: 5)
  - Slobodskoi, Serafim, Reverend, 1955 (Folder 20: 6)
  - Smol'nikov, Nikolai, 1953 (Folder 20: 7)
  - Sobolev, General, 1962-1963 (Folder 20: 8)
  - Soin, Timofei, Reverend, 1952-1955 (Folder 20: 9)
  - Sokhranov, Georgii, 1960 (Folder 20: 10)
  - Sokolov, Gavriil, Reverend, 1967 (Folder 20: 11)
  - Solntsev, Nikolai Pavlovich, 1960-1961 and undated (Folder 20: 12)
  - Soloviev, Pavel, 1952-1955 (Folder 20: 13)
  - Spivakov, Aleksandr Evgrafovich, 1952-1959 (Folder 20: 14)
  - Spivakova, Mariia Nikolaevna, 1967 (Folder 20: 15)
  - Stankevich, Fedor Savvich, 1961 (Folder 20: 16)
  - Staritskii, Vladimir Ivanovich, 1950-1963 (Folder 20: 17)
  - Stefan (Sevbo), Archbishop, 1956-1957 (Folder 20: 18)
  - Stefanov, P., 1953 (Folder 20: 19)
  - Stogov, Petr Evgrafovich, 1958-1961 (Folder 20: 20)
  - Sudkov, G. N. (Folder 20: 21)
  - Sukalo, Aleksandr Stefanovich, 1945-1956 (Folder 20: 22)
  - Sukharevich, V., 1956 (Folder 20: 23)
  - Sulatskii, Ivan Fedorovich, 1953-1957 (Folder 20: 24)
  - Surek, Ina, 1955-1964 (Folder 20: 25)
  - Surovetskii, Boris Vasil'evich, 1955-1958 (Folder 20: 26)
  - Sushkov, Mr., 1952 (Folder 20: 27)
  - Sushkova, Tamara Stepanovna, 1953-1965 (Folder 20: 28)
  - Suzhin, Leonid Ivanovich, 1953 (Folder 20: 29)
  - Svechin, Mikhail Andreevich, 1962-1965 (Folder 20: 30)
  - Svechnikov, V., 1964 (Folder 20: 31)
  - Svir, Boris, 1954-1956 (Folder 21: 1)
  - Svir, Ol'ga Konstantinovna, 1962-1965 (Folder 21: 2)
  - Svishchev, Ivan Sergeevich, 1955-1967 and undated (Folder 21: 3)
  - Tabun, Aleksandr, 1954-1955 (Folder 21: 4)
  - Talberg, Nikolai Dmitrievich, 1953-1962 (Folder 21: 5)
  - Taptykov, S. I., 1953-1965 (Folder 21: 6)
  - Tat'ianko, I., 1954 (Folder 21: 7)
  - Teakston, Andrei and Sofiia, 1960 (Folder 21: 8)
  - Teliatnikov, N., 1958-1965 (Folder 21: 9)
  - Telukhin, Vasilii Nikolaevich, 1953 and undated (Folder 21: 10)
  - Tereshchenko, Dmitirii Mikhkailovich, 1963-1964 (Folder 21: 11)
  - Testin, Vladimir Nikiforovich, 1953-1968 and undated (Folder 21: 12)
  - Thos. Cook & Son (Bankers), 1964 (Folder 21: 13)
  - Tislenkov, Aleksandr Aleksandrovich, 1956-1964 (Folder 21: 14)
  - Tkachenko, Ivan Denisovich, 1952 (Folder 21: 15)
  - Tkachenko, Vladimir Mikhailovich, 1962 (Folder 21: 16)
  - Tkachev, Boris Ivanovich, 1955-1962 (Folder 21: 17)
  - Tokarev, Grigorii Aleksandrovich
    - 1953-1960 and undated (Folder 21: 18)
    - 1961-1963 (Folder 21: 19)
  - Tolstoy Foundation, 1952-1966 (Folder 22: 1)
  - Tolmachev, A. S., 1963 (Folder 22: 2)
  - Tol'chinskaia, Vera, 1957 (Folder 22: 3)
  - Tombieva, Valentina Ivanovna, 1953 (Folder 22: 4)
  - Tretiakov, Vladimir K., 1963-1968 and undated (Folder 22: 5)
  - Triapkin, B., 1955-1957 (Folder 22: 6)
  - Tropin, Nikolai Nikolaevich, 1952-1967 (Folder 22: 7)
  - Trubchaninov, Nikolai Sergeevich, 1967-1969 (Folder 22: 8)
  - Trubetskoi, Vladimir Petrovich, 1953 and undated (Folder 22: 9)
  - Tschebotarioff, Grigorii Porfirovich, 1960-1961 (Folder 22: 10)
  - Tsuglevich, Aleksandr, Reverend, 1968 (Folder 22: 11)
  - Tul'tsev, Mr., undated (Folder 22: 12)
  - Turitsyn, Petr Fedorovich, 1962 (Folder 22: 13)
  - Turoverov, Dmitrii Ivanovich, 1957-1961 (Folder 22: 14)
  - Turoverov, Il'ia Ivanovich, 1953 (Folder 22: 15)
  - Turoverov, Nikolai Nikolaevich, 1948-1950 (Folder 22: 16)
  - Turoverov, Sergei Ivanovich, 1953-1857 (Folder 22: 17)
  - Ukolov, Kharlaampii Matveevich, 1953-1959 (Folder 22: 18)
  - Udal'tsov, Leonid, 1956 (Folder 22: 19)
  - Ulanov, B. N., 1954 and undated (Folder 22: 20)
  - Umnov, Gleb Konstantinovich, 1955-1962 and undated (Folder 22: 21)
  - Urusova, Nataliia Vladimirovna, 1952 and undated (Folder 22: 22)
  - Vakhanevich, Vsevolod Aleksandrovich, 1964 and undated (Folder 22: 23)
  - Varlamov, Ivan Konstantinovich, 1955-1956 (Folder 22: 24)
  - Vasil'ev, Evgenii Vladimirovich, 1953-1956 (Folder 22: 25)
  - Vasilevskaia, Evgeniia, 1967 (Folder 22: 26)
  - Vdorkin, Nikolai Alekseevich, 1955 (Folder 22: 27)
  - Vedernikov, Pavlin Petrovich, 1955-1958 and undated (Folder 22: 28)
  - Verkhovskii, Roman, 1956-1962 (Folder 22: 29)
  - Verkhovskii, S., 1956 and undated (Folder 22: 30)
  - Veselovskii, Vladimir Aleksandrovich, 1957-1968 (Folder 22: 31)
  - Vestnik pervopokhodnika, 1962 (Folder 22: 32)
  - Viatkina, Mariia Davidovna, 1959 (Folder 22: 33)
  - Viktorin (Liabakh), Abbott, 1957 (Folder 22: 34)
  - Vinkler, Emil, 1956 (Folder 22: 35)
  - Vishnevskii, Boris Vladimirovich, 1953-1958 and undated (Folder 22: 36)
  - Visokovskii, Nikolai, 1961 (Folder 22: 37)
  - Vitalii (Maksimenko), Archbishop, 1956-1959 (Folder 22: 38)
  - Vitkovskii, Vladimir Konstantinovich, 1953-1959 (Folder 22: 39)
  - Vladimir (?), Archimandrite, 1965 (Folder 22: 40)
  - Vladimirov, Dmitrii Nikolaevich, 1955-1964 and undated (Folder 23: 1)
  - Vladimirskii, Aleksandr, Reverend, 1950-1969 (Folder 23: 2)
  - Vlasenkov, Fedor, Reverend, 1949 (Folder 23: 3)
  - Volkov, Al. P., 1954 and undated (Folder 23: 4)
  - Volkova-Muromtsova, Varvara Petrovna, 1951 (Folder 23: 5)
  - Volokov, Trofim Andreevich, 1965 (Folder 23: 6)
  - Voloshenova (Korolkova), Nadezhda Bonifatievna, 1953 (Folder 23: 7)
  - Voronin, Mikhail, 1955 (Folder 23: 8)
  - Voronkov, Dmitrii Illarionovich, 1962 (Folder 23: 9)
  - Voropanov, Nikolai Fedorovich, 1961 (Folder 23: 10)
  - Vygran, Vladimir Nikolaevich, 1958-1967 (Folder 23: 11)
  - Vysochin, B. P., 1959 (Folder 23: 12)
  - Weber, Lev Fedorovich and Tatiana Aleksandrovna, 1953-1960 (Folder 23: 13)
  - Weinbischof, Johannes, undated (Folder 23: 14)
  - Wreden, Nicholas, 1954 (Folder 23: 15)
  - Zabaikal'skaia kazach'ia stanitsa, 1962 and undated (Folder 23: 16)
  - Zabolotkin, I., 1955-1956 (Folder 23: 17)
  - Zabuldygin, Pantelei Dmitrievich, 1952-1957 (Folder 23: 18)
  - Zakhanevich, Vsevolod Aleksandrovich, 1952-1968 (Folder 23: 19)
  - Zakharevskii, G., 1958 (Folder 23: 20)
  - Zakharov, Anatolii, 1956-1962 (Folder 23: 21)
  - Zaleskii, Mikhail Nikolaevich, 1952-56 (Folder 23: 22)
  - Zaporozhtsev, Nikolai Semenovich, 1956-1960 (Folder 23: 23)
  - Zaretskii, Mikhail Ivanovich, 1953-1961 (Folder 23: 24)
  - Zavalishin, S., 1958 (Folder 23: 25)
  - Zeber, V., 1955 (Folder 23: 26)
  - Zensikov, M. A., undated (Folder 23: 27)
  - Zershchikov, M., 1952-1961 (Folder 23: 28)
  - Zharov, Sergei, 1953-1964 (Folder 23: 29)
  - Zharskii, Ioann, Reverend, 1962 (Folder 23: 30)
  - Zheliabin, K., 1958 (Folder 23: 31)
  - Zheromskii, G., 1965 (Folder 23: 32)
  - Znamenskii, Georgii Aleksandrovich, 1958 (Folder 23: 33)
  - Zvezdin, I., 1953 and undated (Folder 23: 34)
  - Zubakin, Aleksei, 1956 (Folder 23: 35)
  - Zubov, Nikolai Grigor'evich, 1950-1966 and undated (Folder 23: 36)
  - Zucchini, Marco, 1966-1967 (Folder 23: 37)
- Speeches and writings, 1952-1969 and undated. (Box 24)
  Articles, monograph, notes, and speeches, arranged chronologically by title
  - General
    - Bibliography (Folder 24: 1)
    - Letters to the editor, 1954-1965 and undated (Folder 24: 2)
    - Notes
      - General (Folder 24: 3)
      - Anticommunist movements (Folder 24: 4)
      - History of Don Cossacks (Folder 24: 5)
      - Leib-gvardii kazachii ego velichestva polk (Folder 24: 6)
    - Speeches (Folder 24: 7)
  - "A. M. Kaledin,", undated. (Folder 24: 8)
    Holograph
  - "Mirovoe politicheskoe polozhenie i rol' i zadachi russkoi emigratsii,", undated. (Folder 24: 9)
  - "Nemnogo istoricheskoi pravdy,", undated. (Folder 24: 10)
    Typescript
  - "Psikhologicheskaia podgotovka k vozdushnym napadeniiam,", undated. (Folder 24: 11)
  - "Psikhologicheskaia voina,", undated. (Folder 24: 12)
  - "Vospominaniia A. F. Kerenskogo,", undated. (Folder 24: 13)
    Typescript. Includes newspaper clipping on same topic
  - "Kievskaia Rus',", 1952. (Folder 24: 14)
  - "Popravki v stat'e 'Kazakiia',", 1952. (Folder 24: 15)
    Typescript. Includes clipping of reviewed article
  - Krasnov-Vlasov: vospominaniia, 1959-1969 and undated
    - Correspondence, 1959-1969 and undated (Folder 24: 16)
    - Reviews, 1959-1961 and undated (Folder 24: 17)
  - Donskie kazaki v bor'be s bol'shevikami, 1962
    - Correspondence, 1963-1969 (Folder 24: 18)
    - Typescript, 1961. (Folder 24: 19-20)
      Includes handwritten corrections
    - Reviews, 1962-1963 and undated (Folder 25: 1)
  - "Vynuzhdennoe raz"iasnenie,", 1963. (Folder 25: 2)
    Typescript. Includes related correspondence
- Subject file, 1945-1968 and undated.
  Announcements, appeals, circulars, clippings, correspondence, declarations, minutes, notes, open letters, pamphlets, statutes, typescript, pamphlets, arranged alphabetically by subject
  - American Committee for the Liberation of the Peoples of Russia. Appeals, correspondence, declarations, statutes., 1952-1957 and undated. (Folder 25: 3)
    See also Correspondence/American Committee for Liberation, and Correspondence/Sargeant, Howland
  - Don Cossacks in emigration
    - General (Folder 25: 4)
    - Announcements, appeals, open letters (Folder 25: 5)
    - Ataman elections in the diaspora.
      Includes circulars, clippings and correspondence
      - 1953-1954 and undated (Folder 25: 6)
      - 1955
        - General, 1955 (Folder 25: 7)
        - April-June (Folder 25: 8)
        - July-October (Box-folder 26: 1)
      - 1958-1959 (Folder 26: 2)
      - 1960-1961 (Folder 26: 3)
    - Donskoi voiskovoi sovet, 1956. (Folder 26: 4)
      Includes correspondence
    - Lienz, Austria. (Folder 26: 5)
      Materials on the forced repatriation of Cossacks in 1945
    - Soiuz donskikh kazakov v Amerike. (Folder 26: 6)
      Includes correspondence and minutes
    - Tschebotarioff, Gregory P., 1961-1962. (Folder 26: 7)
      Printed copies of addresses and speeches
    - Tsentr pomoshchi kazakam v Evrope, 1952 and undated (Folder 26: 8)
  - Ioann (Maksimovich), Archbishop, 1963 (Folder 26: 9)
  - Obshchestvo pomoshchi russkim voennym invalidam zarubezh'ia v Amerike. (Folder 26: 10)
    Includes clippings, correspondence and statutes, 1959-1968 and undated
  - Russkii obshche-voinskii soiuz (ROVS), 1950. (Folder 26: 11)
    Minutes Nos. 3, 4
  - Russia. Armiia. Kubanskoe kazach'e voisko. "Vazhneishie sobytiia istorii kubanskogo voiska,", undated (Folder 26: 12)
    typescript
  - Union of Russian Jurists Former DPs in the USA (Folder 26: 13)
  - Vlasov, Andrei Andreevich. (Folder 26: 14)
    Clippings
- Miscellany, undated. (Box 27)
  Clippings, duplicates, notes. Not filmed. Originals retained by Holy Trinity Seminary
- Photographs. (Box 28)
  Two photo albums, 145 prints depicting White Army generals and officers, émigré activists, clergy, and social functions. Not filmed. Originals retained by Holy Trinity Seminary